# JARRETÉ BARNETT

jy.barnett.io@gmail.com



(860) 614-9019



South Windsor, CT 06074

## **SKILLS**

- CSS \*\*\*\*\*
- HTML \*\*\*\*\*
- SQL \*\*\*\*\*
- Git ★★★★★
- JavaScript ★★★★
- jQuery ★★★★
- Node.JS ★★★★
- React ★★★★
- Angular ★★★★
- TypeScript ★★★★
- MongoDB ★★★
- Java ★★★

# **EDUCATION**

**University of Connecticut** 

Storrs, CT • 07/2021

Certification: Full Stack Software Engineering

**Central Connecticut State University** 

No Degree: Liberal Arts And General Studies Howell Cheney Technical High School

High School Diploma

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- UConn Coding Bootcamp
- Woz-U Application Development & Java Intensive Program

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An experienced Full Stack Software Engineer with background in building and maintaining server database applications, as well as client-side rendering for intuitive and responsive operating systems. Proven analytical and problem-solving abilities, supported by intensive training and verifiable certifications in software engineering and server-side computer sciences. Versatile working habits suited for either team-oriented or remote work conditions. Established track record for pursuing new challenges, including those involving opportunities to learn new technologies, languages, coding libraries and frameworks.

# WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- jarretebarnett.github.io
- linkedin.com/in/jarretebarnett
- twitter.com/jarretedotio

#### WORK HISTORY

Turnberry Solutions - Software Engineer Associate I

St. Louis, MO • 05/2022 - Current

- Team is tasked with the responsibility of developing and refining Pay with Rewards features
  which offers users redemption rewards for eligible purchases.
- Make daily collaborative effort with product managers to designate top priority stories that can be managed and completed within current or upcoming sprints and iterations.
- Granted access to company repositories to modify applications and files as needed in order to
  optimize configuration and functionality, as well as eliminate any conflicting or obsolete code.
- Discuss best practices with team members when necessary, and commit to bi-weekly elaborations on anemic design stories.

# William Raveis Real Estate Inc. - Licensed Real Estate Sales Associate

Avon, CT • 02/2020 - Current

- Manage a personal CRM database of customers and clients.
- · Marketing for social media-centric engagement, reaching hundreds of active users monthly.
- Prospecting inventory for seller interest, market data, and inquiring customers planning to buy or
  rent

#### The Coder School - Instructional Coach

Glastonbury, CT • 11/2021 - 04/2022

- Provide support to students who are learning new software frameworks and languages.
- Relay notes of progress to both parents and internal administration.
- Refine students' skills in languages such as Python, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, etc.

### Keller Williams Realty - Licensed Real Estate Sales Associate

Glastonbury, CT • 07/2019 - 01/2020

- Consultative experience with sellers inquiring about the marketability of their homes relative to
  existing inventory and proximity.
- Managed client expectations proceeding closings, as well as the technical diligence required to research relevant property data for customers.
- Closed over \$200,000 of volume within the first three months of licensure.
- Effectively closed home purchases expediently in a six-week timeframe.